A man in search. A woman in need. A story of fate.
A Walk in the Clouds is a drama, romance film directed by Alfonso Arau.
World War II vet Paul Sutton falls for a pregnant and unwed woman who persuades him -- during
their first encounter -- to pose as her husband so she can face her family.
Paul Sutton, played by Keanu Reeves.
Victoria Aragón, played by Aitana Sánchez-Gijón.
Don Pedro Aragón, played by Anthony Quinn.
María José Aragón, played by Angélica Aragón.
Guadelupe Aragón, played by Evangelina Elizondo.
Betty Sutton, played by Debra Messing.
A Walk in the Clouds is a 1995 period romantic drama film directed by Alfonso Arau and starring Keanu Reeves, Aitana
Sánchez-Gijón, Giancarlo Giannini, Angélica Aragón, Evangelina Elizondo, Debra Messing and Anthony Quinn.
An international co-production film between the United States and Mexico, it was an
English-language remake of the 1942 Italian film Four Steps in the Clouds.
A Walk in the Clouds was released in theaters on
August 11, 1995, by 20th Century Fox.
It received mixed reviews from critics, but it was a commercial
success, grossing $91 million against a $20 million budget.
Maurice Jarre’s musical score earned him a Golden
Globe Award for Best Original Score.
The film explores themes of pregnancy, world war ii, vineyard, love, remake.
The tone is emotional.